<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Todd Martin Real Estate Training Blog</title>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from -- CLIENT BRAND -- - your professional -- MARKET -- Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 11:58:42 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 11:58:42 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Now a Good Time to Start Your Career in Real Estate?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/99lF8vw04SQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lately, a lot of people have been asking, “Is now the right time to jump into the real estate market?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would absolutely say yes. Why? The current market is phenomenal. We are coming off some amazing gains and the best real estate market we’ve seen in awhile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a lot of pent-up frustration from buyers who have been in the market for the last year trying to find a home. Due to low inventory, many buyers have not been able to make a purchase yet. Not only that, interest rates are slowly creeping up, so we have plenty of people ready to buy a home. &lt;strong&gt;Our team has a lot of business going right now.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We need new team members to help us with all of this great business!%20localhost:4000/is-now-a-good-time-to-start-your-career-in-real-estate.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We need new team members to help us with all of this great business!”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we come into the first of the year, there are some great grant programs available for first-time buyers, so we have a lot of options to help home buyers in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said, if you’re interested in a career with the Todd Martin Group, &lt;strong&gt;we are looking for someone to join our team.&lt;/strong&gt; We need someone to help us manage all of this great business! Plus, our Guaranteed Lead Program will get you 30 to 50 leads a month. We will also show you how to convert those leads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/versions/bigstock-real-estate-agent-4574436---x----900-506x---.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;image-size&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, if you’re ready to jump into the real estate market or start your real estate career, give me a call or send me an email. I hope to hear from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/is-now-a-good-time-to-start-your-career-in-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/is-now-a-good-time-to-start-your-career-in-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate Career</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
